杰森∶亲爱的,我在想,
Jason: Oh sa-weet heart.
开萝尔还在工作,克莉丝在睡觉,
You know, i was just thinking, with Carol working late and Chrissy asleep,
本不知道在外面干着什么天知道的事情,家里就只有我们自己了.
Bens out doing god knows what, you and I have this whole house to ourselves.
麦琪∶杰森,外面还没有黑呢.
Maggie: Jason, its not even dark out.
杰森∶我知道.
Jason: I know.
麦琪∶宝贝儿,不能再等等吗?我最爱的就是重新拍摄的卡格雷和啦斯.
Maggie: Honey, can't it wait?This is my favorite re run of Cagney and Lacey
电视∶打那个小丑!
TV: Spread em clown!
杰森∶没关系.
Jason: Never mind.
本∶你为什么要打我?
Ben: What did you hit me for?
麦琪∶听起来你儿子发生事故了.
Maggie: Sounds like your son is in trouble again.
杰森∶让他进来看卡格雷和啦斯.
Jason: Lets get him in here and watch Cagney and Lacey.
杰森∶外面到底发生了什么事情?
Jason: What the heck is going on out here?
麦琪∶为什么车道上都是沙子?外面有40度呢.
Maggie: And why is there sand all over the driveway?And its forty degrees out.
你们这些女孩穿着游泳衣在干什么?
What are you girls doing in bathing suits?
女孩∶因为我们是愚不可及,相信本是一个认真的导演,
Girl: because we were stupid enough to believe that Ben was a serious
就像斯威斯特一样.
filmmaker, like Sylvester Stallone.
女孩们∶耶!
Girls: Yeah!
麦琪∶本,你有什么要解释的吗?
Maggie: Ben, what do you have to say for yourself?
本∶唷.
Ben: Yo.
女孩∶让我们走,女士们.
Girl: Let's go ladies.
杰森∶说话.
Jason: Talk now.
本∶我只是完成我的英语课的电影,
Ben: well, see, I was just finishing my movie for English class,
因为劳拉林认为我是在拍电影,
when Laura-Lynn got the crazy idea that I was just doing the movie so
所以我就...
I could um,..
女孩∶这样你就可以摸我.
Girl: So you could grope me.
本∶如果你想走,你就走.女人都是疯子.
Ben: If you are going to leave.Leave.Women can be so nuts.
麦琪∶错怪妈妈了,本.
Maggie: Wrong parent Ben.
本∶女人能这么疯.
Ben: Women can be so nuts.
杰森∶本,错误的车道.
Jason: Wrong drive way Ben.
麦琪∶本,我以为你打算做一部关于我的记录片.
Maggie: Ben, I thought you were going to do a documentary about me.
一个参加工作的母亲设法去平衡事业和家庭.
A working mother trying to balance career and home.
本∶面对现实,没人会对这个感兴趣.
Ben: Face it mum.No one's interested in that.
麦琪∶所以你就选择了某些值得做的事情,比如说拍女孩穿泳装.
Maggie: So you passed up something worthwhile like that to do girls in
杰森,你可以相信这些吗?
bathing suits.Ha, Jason can you believe this?
杰森∶本,你妈妈讲到了重点.
Jason: Your mothers got a point Ben.
拍一部无聊的电影不会有什么问题.
There's nothing wrong with doing a boring movie.
杰森∶本,我们想马上看看你的小电影.
Jason: well Ben, we better see this little movie right now.
本∶我还没有最好呢.
Ben: There's a lot of stuff on that tape I haven't edited out yet.
麦琪∶是的,我肯定是...
Maggie: Yeah, I bet there is.
开萝尔∶你们在看什么?
Carol: What are you guys watching?
麦琪∶本的英语课的电影.
Maggie: Ben's movie for English class.
开萝尔∶什么,本,你不是说过等完成后,要先让我看看效果的吗?
Carol: What, Ben, you said you'd tell me when it was done so I could
see how I'd come out
麦琪∶所以你知道,知道他没有拍关于我的记录片了?
Maggie: So you knew.You knew he wasn't making the documentary about me too?
开萝尔∶当爸爸让他别拍时,我也在.
Carol: Well I was there when dad talked him out of it.
杰森∶爆米花.
Jason: Popcorn.
麦琪∶杰森,我们正打算开始了.
Maggie: Jason, we are about to start the tape.
杰森∶本,等级评定为R.你得承认很下流的.
Jason: Ben, its rated R.Come on.You admit it's dirty.
本∶不是的.
Ben: No I don't.
Its just no kid wants to watch a movie anymore if its not rated R
迈克∶本,你的电影等级是R?我也要看看了..
Mike: Ah Ben, your movie is rated R?I'm watching it
(本的电影)佛罗里达.1978年的夏天.
(Ben's movie) Florida.The Summer of 1978.
.迈克∶麦琪,就像你的丈夫杰森所说,
Mike: Well Maggie, speaking as your husband Jason,
.那肯定是一个非常美妙的佛罗里达假期.
it sure has been a great Florida vacation.
.1978年,我们是典型的美国家庭.
Considering its 1978 and we are a typical American family
开萝尔∶我是一个职业妈妈,设法去平衡事业和家庭.
Carol: And me being a working mum trying to balance a career and a home.
(回到现实世界)
(Back to the real world)
麦琪∶那个被认为是我们吗?
Maggie: Is that supposed to be us?
本∶恩....
Ben: Well..
杰森∶如果以你真正的父母为题材来拍电影,
Jason: Seems like it just would have been simpler to just write your movie
事情就会简单很多了.
parents like your real parents.
本∶他们在开玩笑?
Ben: They're kidding right?
迈克∶你要么接受,要么就拒绝.
Mike: Either you get it or you don't.
(本的电影)
(Ben's film)
迈克∶是的.
Mike: Yup yup yup yup yup.
开萝尔∶杰森,一切都是如此的完美.阳光,
Carol: Jason, everything is so perfect.
好时光,橘子.什么地方搞错了呢?
The sunshine, the good times, the oranges.What could possibly go wrong?
迈克∶嘿麦琪!50美分一条小鳄鱼.
Mike: Hey Maggie look!Baby alligators for fifty cents each.
鳄鱼,小家伙,他叫什么名字?
Alligator, little uh, uh, what's his name?
开萝尔∶杰森,这就是我们在讨论的我们的儿子.
Carol: Jason, that is our son you are talking about.
迈克∶给多点暗示.
Mike: Give me a little bit more of a hint than that.
本∶停止全部的锤打!我们要试着拍电影了.
Ben: Hey, stop all the hammering!We're trying to make a movie here.
(十分钟以后)
(Ten minutes later)
开萝尔∶小鳄鱼太可爱了.
Carol: Ah, the baby alligator is so cute.
迈克∶没错.麦琪,
Mike: Yeah, and the best part Maggie, is that I got a ten percent discount.
更好玩的是因为只有一只眼睛,所以我只用40美分就买下来了.
They only have one eye.
开萝尔∶什么?我们把小的猫尾草忘在了鳄鱼农场.
Carol: What?We forgot baby timothy at the alligator farm.
迈克∶小什么?
Mike: Baby who?
开萝尔∶我们的儿子杰森.
Carol: Our son Jason.
(本西维尔介绍∶恐怖片,本西维尔的电影.主演本西维尔.监制本西维尔,导演本西维尔,剧本本西维尔.根据本西维尔的原遍概念改编.音乐的创作是由其他人负责的,由本西维尔选择的.全部在西维尔工作室由本西维尔拍摄完成.与本西维尔监制合作出品)
(Ben Seaver Presents: The Horror, A Film by Ben Seaver.Starring Ben Seaver.Produced by Ben Seaver.Directed by Ben Seaver, Screenplay by Ben Seaver.Based on an original concept by Ben Seaver.Original music by some other dude, chosen by Ben Seaver.Shot entirely at Seaver Studios by Ben Seaver.In association with Ben Seaver Productions)
开萝尔∶本,我们中的一些人也有角色呢.
Carol: Ben, some of us have parts too.
本∶穿上你的衣服.
Ben: Keep your shirt on.
迈克∶请吧.
Mike: Yes please.
(克瑞丝西维尔,开萝尔西维尔,维特和斯提克,迈克西维尔)
(With, Chrissy Seaver, Carol Seaver, Veto and Stinky Sullivan, Mike Seaver)
本∶高兴了吧?
Ben: Happy now?
(本的电影)
(Ben's film)
(自从佛罗里达后,12年)
(Twelve years since Florida)
迈克∶1990年,
Mike: well honey, being your husband Jason,
对作为你丈夫的我杰森来说,是一个美好的日子,
it sure is a beautiful day for nineteen ninety,
我们变成了一个典型的美国家庭.
being a typical American family.
开萝尔∶杰森宝贝儿,它不是...
Carol: Jason honey, wasn't it...
迈克∶只要一想到我们成为了典型的美国家庭,
Mike: A beautiful day for nineteen ninety,
我就觉得1990年真是太美好了.
considering we are a typical American family.
开萝尔∶杰森,你今天要准备早餐.
Carol: Jason, I thought you were going to make breakfast today.
毕竟,我是一个设法去平衡事业和家庭的职业女性.
I mean after all, I am a working mother trying to balance a career and home.
本∶我需要你们其中的一个在我的成绩单上签字.
Ben: I need one of you guys to sign my report card.
迈克∶我们又不是你的父母?
Mike: well shouldn't it be one of your parents?
本∶你们就是我的父母.
Ben: You guys are my parents.
迈克∶哦,对...
Mike: Oh right, uh, uh...
本∶吉姆.
Ben: Jim.
迈克:是啊,
Mike: Yes Jim.Jim,
吉米,吉米,
my haven't you grown since the last twelve years when we bought that
自从十二年前你买了鳄鱼皮革把它冲进厕所我觉得你就没有长大.
alligator and flushed him down the toilet and haven't thought of since.
开萝尔∶你难道不认为我们应该好好的检查一下他的成绩单,在我们签字前?
Carol: Don't you think we should check his report card before we sign it?
迈克∶为什么?小蒂姆的表现一向都很好的.
Mike: Why?Little Tim has turned out just fine.
本∶吉姆!吉姆!
Ben: Jim!Jim!
迈克∶是我们给你起的名字,所以,
Mike: We named you, we can change it.
我们也可以改变它.
Well son, to show you that I have no hard feelings about these selfish
为了表现我对你的大度,我决定奖赏你的这些C,
outbursts, I'm going to reward you for all these fine C's.
我们夫妇可以帮你收拾肉,还,
Here's a, here's a couple for, uh, for six cents off tidy flesh,
可以节约6美分,
which you can use to clean the toilet bowl where we flushed the alligator
这样,你就可以用6美分去打扫12年前的冲走鳄鱼的马桶.
twelve years ago and haven't thought of since.
女孩∶从这里开始吗?不.
Girl: Start right here?No.
本∶你干什么?如果你住口的话,我们才会拍摄这些东西.
Ben: What are you doing?If you just shut up, we'll shoot this thing.
本∶对不起,我来晚了.比尔克林小姐,给你我的成绩单.成绩单.
Ben: Sorry I'm late Miss Birkin.Here's my report card.Report card.
迈克(演教师)∶你是来这里的吗?
Mike (playing teacher): You, boy.Do you go here?
本∶我是吉姆詹金.
Ben: I'm Jim Jenkins.
迈克∶吉姆.你在我的班里已经呆了多久了?
Mike: Jim.Well how long have you been in my class?
本∶8年.
Ben: Eight years.
迈克∶8年!那我怎么以前都没有见到过你?
Mike: Eight years!How come I've never seen you before?
本∶你见过我了.每天我们都要有一次这样的对话.
Ben: You have seen me.Every day when we have this conversation.
迈克∶不要那么的软弱.
Mike: Oh, well then stop being so lamb.
本∶是.我肯定是老了.
Ben: Yes mam.Well this is getting old.
我的父母不认识我,我的老师也不认识我.
My parents don't know me, my teacher doesn't know me..
臭虫∶你不能坐在那里.我的最好的朋友吉姆詹金通常要坐在那里的.
Stinky: You can't sit there.My best friend Jim Jenkins usually sits there.
本∶我是吉姆詹金.
Ben: I am Jim Jenkins.
臭虫∶抱歉吉姆,你很难让人记住.
Stinky: Sorry Jim, you're just so darn forgettable.
本∶臭虫,但是我不会忘记你是谁.
Ben: Well I don't forget who you are, skunky.
臭虫∶那是因为我很臭.
Stinky: That's because I smell.
本:芭比来了.
Ben: Oh, oh, here comes Bambie.The hottest most beautiful girl in school.
超级美丽的小花.她有五点八英寸的身体,
She's got the body of a five foot eight inch beauty on a four foot eight
四点八英寸的骨架.
inch frame.
芭比∶你不会用这个,对吗?
Bambi: You're not going to use that are you?
本∶她不但美丽,而且聪明.
Ben: Not only is she beautiful, she's smart.
她是集机智,
She's today's woman with the right combination of savvy,
格调和技巧于一身的现代女性.她的光环让我眼花缭乱.
style and sophistication.And the giddiness that makes me dizzy.
芭比∶你是谁?
Bambi: Who are you?
本∶我是吉姆詹金.我已经和你同学8年了.
Ben: I'm Jim Jenkins.I've been going to school with you for eight years.
在你还没有长胸前,我就认识你了.
I knew you before you had breasts.
臭虫∶我一直都有胸.
Stinky: I've always had breasts.
本∶住口臭虫.那是她的台词.
Ben: Shut up Stinky.That's her line.
芭比∶我是不会说这句台词的.
Bambi: I'm not going to say that Ben.
(在现实生活中)
(In real life)
本∶胸部是小鸡的一部分,我相信也是最受欢迎的一部分..
Ben: A breast is a part of a chicken.The most popular part I believe
迈克∶本,你不是在帮你自己.
Mike: Bennie, you're not helping yourself here.
(本的电影)
(Ben's film)
芭比∶我有一个行头的问题.我为什么要在班上穿游泳衣?
Bambi: I have a wardrobe question.Why am I wearing a bathing suit in class?
本∶因为下课后你要去海滩上.
Ben: Because you are going to the beach after.
芭比∶但是,我的角色可以知道这点吗?
Bambi: But would my character know that yet?
本∶劳拉;,劳拉,劳拉,
Ben: Laura, Laura, Laura.See, this girl Bambie isn't like you at all.
知道了吧,这个女孩芭比可一点也不像你.她就是一个白痴.
See, she's just a dumb bimbo.
芭比∶但是你说她是集机智,时髦,和久经世故于一身的女人.
Bambi: But you said she was a savvy, stylish, sophisticated woman.
本∶不是我说的.是吉姆说的.
Ben: I didn't say that.Jim said that.See he was just lying.
他在撒谎.他会想尽一切办法来摸摸她.
He'd do anything just to get a chance to grope her.
芭比∶那个卑鄙的人!
Bambi: That sleaze!
本∶他也很让我恶心,但是,我还是会尽力演好他的.
Ben: Hey, he disgusts me too, but I'll do my best to play him.
本∶好了,开始.
Ben: Ok, action.Great, when is mike going to get this stinking thing fixed?
当迈克正在修理坏掉的东西的时候,我们洗掉刚才拍的,重新来一遍.
Let's just erase it and start over.
臭虫∶不要清洗掉.我们可以把它寄给美国最有趣家庭...
Stinky: Don't erase it.We'll send it to Americas funniest home vide....
大家都不记得我的名字了.我讨厌学校,我认为我该退学才对.
And everyone forgetting my name.I hate school.I think I'm going to drop out.
臭虫∶别傻了.
Stinky: don't be a fool.Stay in school.
留在学校.退学就像是把自己的未来用马桶冲走一样,
Drop outs just take their future and drop it down the toilet.
就像那条独眼的鳄鱼.
Much like that one eyed alligator.
本∶哦!太好了!
Ben: Oh, oh great!
臭虫∶别傻了!留在学校.
Stinky: Don't be a fool.Stay in school.
退学就像是把自己的未来用马桶冲走一样,
Drop outs just take their future and drop, drop it...Don't be a fool.
就像那条独眼的鳄鱼.留在学校.
Stay in school.Drop outs just take their future and flush it down the toilet.
退学就像是把自己的未来用马桶冲走一样,
Much like that one eyed alligator your parents bought for you twelve years
就像那条独眼的鳄鱼,自从你父母12年前把你买回来后再也没有想过你.
ago and never thought of since.
本∶谢谢臭虫.很高兴能和你谈谈,我会继续留在学校的.
Ben: Thanks stinky.I'm glad we had this little talk.I'm going to stay in school.
臭虫∶说到眼花缭乱,你想首先谈论金发碧眼的还是红色的?
Stinky: Speaking of dizzy, do you want to talk about blondes first, or red heads?
本∶我不管我们考虑谁.要忠实于剧本,
Ben: I don't care who we think about.
找到我心目中的美丽的芭比.
I just got to get my mind of the beautiful Bambi.Just stick to the script.
臭虫∶我相信总有一天吉姆,你会做一些引起她注意的事情.一些轰动的失去.
Stinky: I'm sure some day Jim, you'll do something to make her notice you.
伟大的事情.到那时,
Something big.Something great.Till then, you can dream.
你就可以做梦了.我要去上大号了.啊!!!
I have to go to the can.Ahhh!Urgh!!!
本:只是打开窗子.斯库克,你在么?
Ben: At least open the window crack in there dude.Skunky!
斯库克!斯库克!!
Skunky, are you ok in there?Skunky!Skunky!!!!!Skunky, what happened?
斯库克,怎么了?你只剩下头了.
You're just a head.
臭虫∶一条鳄鱼从厕所里面爬出来,然后吃掉了我.
Stinky: An alligator came out of the toilet and ate me.
本∶你为何不跑?
Ben: Why didn't you run?
臭虫:我没有看到他来.
Stinky: I didn't see him coming.I don't have eyes in the back of my head.
我没有长后眼.
Come to think of it.I don't have anything in the back of my head.
想想吧.吉米,
Jim, I only have time to give you this one warning.
我只是警告你.
All the alligators that were flushed down the toilets,
那些把鳄鱼冲进厕所从此不被家长重视的孩子,
by American parents who haven't thought of them since,
已经不见了.
have come home to roost!
迈克∶作为你的丈夫.我很高兴我们有一个典型的美国式家庭.
Mike: Well, as you're husband Maggie,
有2辆车,
I'm sure glad that we have a typical American family.
有漂亮房子,
With two cars, a beautiful home and a child of some sorts.
还有小孩子,和一个大绿色的狗.
And a big green dog.
本∶爸爸,妈妈!
Ben: Mum, dad!Skunky Mulligan just got eaten by an alligator that climbed
臭虫被从厕所里爬出来的鳄鱼吃掉恶劣,你们快自行逃命吧!
out of our toilet.Run for your lives!
迈克∶对不起,年轻人,
Mike: Well if you are..I'm sorry young man.
但是我们的儿子现在真的不在家,不能和你一起玩.
Our son isn't here to play with you.
本:是的.
Ben: I am.Skunky Mulligan just got eaten by a gator that came out of our
臭虫刚刚被从厕所里出来的鳄鱼给吃了.
toilet.
迈克∶如果你是我们的儿子的话,你就应该知道我的名字不是吉姆.而是杰森.
Mike: I'm sorry young man, but our son isn't here to play with you.
本:我是你的儿子,吉米.
Ben: I am your son.Jim.
迈克:如果你是我们的儿子,应该知道我不叫吉米.我叫杰森.
Mike: Well if you are our son, you would know my name isn't Jim.It's Jason.
开萝尔∶这是我们的儿子杰森.
Carol: This is our son Jason.
迈克∶我们没有儿子叫杰森的,那是我的名字.
Mike: We don't have a son Jason.That's my name.
本∶在你们试图想出你是谁的时候,
Ben: While you two are trying to figure out who you are,
一条鳄鱼可能已经爬进客厅了.
an alligator could come through the living room.
迈克∶如果它着的爬到客厅,我们的大绿色狗会解决它.
Mike: well if it did, our big green dog would get him.
本∶啊!
Ben: Ahhhhh!
本∶我的父母不愿相信我,其他也没有人知道我是谁.
Ben: my parents wouldn't believe me and no one else knows who I am.
那我要告诉谁呢?话务员.
Who can I tell about this?Operator.Give me the number for nine one one.
请帮我接911.是的.
Oh yeah.
迈克∶(演布什总统)我是布什总统.
Mike: (as President Bush) This is President Bush.
本∶你打911的时候就会接通总统吗?
Ben: That's what you get when you dial nine one one?
迈克∶我讨厌浪费时间.到现在,已经是1点15分30秒了.
Mike: well I got tired of giving out the time.By the time, its one fifteen and thirty seconds.
本∶看总统先生,一个重大的危险正在威胁整个星球.
Ben: Look, Mr.President.A grave danger threatens the whole planet.
到处都是鳄鱼.
There are alligators everywhere.
迈克∶呼.又是副总统,衢尔吧,对吗?
Mike: Hu.This is Vice President Quail again, isn't it?
本∶不,我是吉姆詹金,我说的是真的.我...
Ben: No, this is Jim Jenkins and I'm serious.Ok?Look, I,
迈克∶(提示他)你需要帮助,给军队打电话.
Mike: (prompting him) You got to help, call the army.
本∶我需要你的帮助.海军,甚至空军.
Ben: You got to help.Call the army .The navy.Even the air force.
迈克∶作为你的总统,我保证你,
Mike: Now as your President,
没有什么可担心的.
let me assure you that you have nothing to worry about.
(尖叫,啊!)
(Screams.ahhh!)
迈克∶Barbara! 芭芭拉!
Mike: (screams.ahhh)
本∶哈罗,哈罗.有人可以听得见我的声音吗?
Ben: Hello, hello.Is there anybody who can hear my voice?
女孩∶跳,跳! 跳!
Girls: jump, jump, jump!
本∶我是不会跳的,傻瓜们.我爬上来是要告诉你们,鳄鱼正在朝这个方向过来.
Ben: Look, I'm not jumping you fools.I just climbed up hear to tell you the gators are heading this way.
女孩们∶啊!
Girls: Ahhh!
本∶哦!太可怕了.
Ben: Oh, the horror.
(在现实生活中)
(Real life)
麦琪∶杰森,我们必须去浴室了.
Maggie: Jason, we have to go to the bathroom.
杰森∶我不去.
Jason: I don't.
麦琪∶你得去.
Maggie: Yes you do.
迈克∶在你坐下前,最好先看看.
Mike: Well look before you sit.
本∶对于看过我电影的人来说,肯定会很长时间不敢去厕所.
Ben: Man, for people who want to see my movie, they are sure taking a long time in the bathroom.
迈克∶本,他们不在厕所.
Mike: Bennie, they are not in the bathroom.
本∶但是他们说他们必须...
Ben: But they said they had to..
迈克∶相信我.这不过是一对老父母的把戏,他们正在谈论你呢.
Mike: Trust me.It's an old parent's trick.They are talking about you.
本∶你认为?
Ben: You think?
开萝尔∶他们有很多关于你的话题要讨论呢,本,你是一只恶心的小狗.
Carol: They have a lot to talk about Ben.You are one sick little puppy.
杰森∶麦琪,你说得对.本现在越来越懂事了.
Jason: Ok Maggie.You were right about Ben.His hornballosity has got out of hand.
麦琪∶杰森,你错了.
Maggie: You are wrong Jason.
杰森∶我同意你的说法,我怎么会是错的呢?
Jason: I agreed with you.How can I be wrong?
麦琪∶我错了.
Maggie: I was wrong.
杰森∶那我没错?
Jason: Then I'm not wrong?
麦琪∶你当然也错了.你没有听到吗?
Maggie: Of course you are.Haven't you been listening?
杰森,
Jason, would Ben spend all this time money and effort with a caste of
你认为本花这么多时间和努力拍摄了成千上万个镜头,真的只是为了能和劳拉林在外面幽会吗?
thousands just to make out with Laura-Lynn?
杰森∶哈哈,我不会.
Jason: ha ha ha.I would.Not Laura-Lynn.
不是劳拉林,如果我还是一个年轻的男孩而你还是一个少女.少女麦琪.
No if I were a young boy and you were a young girl.girl Maggie.
麦琪∶杰森,再想想.
Maggie: Jason, think about it.A kid nobody listens to.
一个没有倾诉对象的孩子.大家,他的父母都忽视了他.
People, his parents ignoring him.So he's got to save the world on his own.
因此他不得不靠自己的力量来拯救世界.这个电影就是为了寻求帮助的.
Honey, this movie is a cry for help.
杰森∶寻求某些东西.
Jason: It's a cry for something.
(本的电影)
(Ben's film)
本∶我在这个壁架上站了一个小时多,想着如果我不能不能拯救世界的话,
Ben: I stood on that ledge for an hour,
那我最少可以科隆一个新的芭比来.
thinking if I couldn't save the world,
幸运的是,我有了一架飞机.
at least I could populate a new one with Bambi.Luckily I had a plane.
飞行员∶引擎看起来没问题.我现在要坐进驾驶员座舱了...
Pilot: Well, the engine looks ok.Now I'll just get into the cockpit and...
开萝尔∶爸爸,你在毁...
Carol: Dad, you're ruining...
本∶让我们看看这个小宝贝能做什么.她能去哪里?她能去哪里呢?
Ben: Ok, let's see what this baby can do.Where could she be?
嘿,她在那里.
Where could she be?Hey, there she is.Looking as fine as ever.
和以前一样,没有任何的变化,身材也还是那么的好.
Five foot eight inch beauty on a four foot eight inch frame.
(在现实生活中)
(Real life)
迈克∶在我看来,看起来更像4英寸的体格.
Mike: That looks more like a four inch frame to me.
(本的电影)
(Ben's film)
本∶他们在那里.我本来应该找个安全的地方再着陆,
Ben: and there they are.
那样的话就会来不及了.为了拯救芭比,
I could look for a safe place to land, then I'd be too late.
我豁出去了.那会是一个侥幸的脱险.
I can risk everything and save Bambi.Boy that was a close call.
希望我没有来迟.大家都快自行逃命.
Hope I'm not late.Hey, everybody run for your lives.
芭比∶你是谁?
Bambi: Who are you?
本∶我是吉姆詹金.我已经和你同学8年了.
Ben: I'm Jim Jenkins.
在你还没有长胸前,我就认识你了.
I have been going to school with you before you had breasts.
芭比∶是的,你是那个可怜的男孩,
Bambi: Oh yeah.You are the lamb boy whose parents flushed the alligator
你的父母就是把鳄鱼冲进厕所后再也没有想起过它的那对夫妇吗?
down the toilet and haven't thought of it since.
本∶没错.鳄鱼回来了,并且很凶残的.
Ben: Yeah, well they are back and they are bad.
女孩∶啊!
Girls: Ahhhh!
本∶嘿,跑也已经来不及了,不过我可以应付,我会保护你们的.
Ben: Hey, there is no time to run now, but I can handle this.I'll protect you.
芭比∶如果你救了我的命,我会万分感激.
Bambi: If you save my life, I'll show you my appreciation.
我不知道他可以这么英勇.他是一个真正的男子汉.
I didn't know he could fight like that.He's such a man.
我感觉自己和他的父母一样傻,这么多年来一直忽略了他.哇,
I feel like such a fool for ignoring him all these years, like his parents do.
你擦擦他的肚子就能让他睡过去?肚子.
Wow, you put him to sleep just by rubbing his belly?Belly.
本∶是的芭比.你想不想睡一会儿?
Ben: Yeah Bambi.You feel like catching a little shut eye too?
芭比∶当心!啊!
Bambi: Watch out!Aghhhhh!
女孩∶啊!
Girls: Ahhh!
迈克(演鳄鱼)∶吉姆.
Mike (Playing Alligator): Jim.
本∶你知道我的名字?在地球上没有人知道我是谁,
Ben: You know my name?
但是你却知道我的名字?
Nobody on earth knows who I am, but you know my name?
迈克∶我是你的鳄鱼,吉姆.记得我吗?冲水啊!
Mike: I was your gator Jim.Remember me.Flush ahhhhh!
本∶你从哪里学会说话的?
Ben: Yeah.Where did you learn to talk?
迈克∶你一定会惊讶于在下水道里有多少东西可以学,吉姆.
Mike: You'd be surprised how much you pick up in the sewers Jim.
本∶你为什么要杀人呢?
Ben: What are you, what are you doing killing people?
迈克∶我们从来没有故意的想要杀人.我们也只是要那些大家都想要的东西.
Mike: We never meant to kill anyone.We just want what everyone wants.
足够的食物,还有抚养我们孩子的好的环境.
Enough to eat.A decent neighborhood to raise our kids in.
少女∶啊!
Girls: Ah!
Mike: And I want this guy here to get an A on this film project
本∶你为什么不游向开阔的水里去呢?在那里的海水都很干净,
Ben: Well, why don't you just swim for the open water,
还有足够多的鱼可以吃.
where the ocean is clean and there are plenty of fish?
迈克∶不错的主意.
Mike: What a great idea.
Ben: And as for me getting an A, its all in Mr.Bloomberg's hands
迈克∶他是个非常棒的人,我知道他不会让我失望的.
Mike: Well, he's a great guy and he won't let me down.Come on guys!
芭比∶吉姆,你是我的英雄.我要怎么来感谢你呢?(他吻她)(她给了他一巴掌)
Bambi: Jim, you are my hero.How can I ever thank you?(He kisses her) (She slaps him)
杰森∶本,你妈妈讲到了重点.
Jason: Well your mothers got a point Ben.
拍一部无聊的电影不会有什么问题.
There's nothing wrong with doing a boring movie.
(在现实生活中)
(Real life)
杰森∶本,够了.这是以我们为原型的.
Jason: That's enough Ben.I think this is where we came in.
本∶嘿,大家都知道摄像机也可以说谎的.
Ben: hey, it's a well known fact that cameras can lie.
杰森∶对,13岁的小男孩也会.
Jason: Yeah, so can thirteen year old boys.
我们要谈谈关于尊敬女人的话题,本.
We are going to have a little talk about respecting women Ben.
麦琪∶杰森,拜托.本,我知道你的真正意图.
Maggie: Jason, please.Ben.I know what you were trying to do.
本∶你知道?
Ben: You do?
麦琪∶是的,你感觉到被忽视和认为自己无关紧要了.
Maggie: Yes.You were feeling ignored and insignificant.
本∶有吗?
Ben: I was?
麦琪∶怎么不会呢?你不是最大的一个,也不是最小的一个,你也不是最聪明的一个.
Maggie: And why shouldn't you?You're not the oldest and you are youngest and you are certainly not the smartest.
本∶妈妈,你让我很沮丧.
Ben: Mum, you are depressing me.
麦琪∶我只是说,我知道你想让我们注意到这部电影.
Maggie: I'm just saying honey, that I know you made this movie to be noticed.
本∶我有吗?
Ben: I did?
麦琪∶如果不是这样的话,那你就真的是个恶心的小狗了.
Maggie: Well it's either that or you are one sick little puppy.
杰森∶那是我所选的答案.
Jason: That's how I vote.
本∶什么?
Ben: What?
杰森∶本,
Jason: Ben, I think you made this movie just so that you could kiss your
我认为你拍这部电影的目的只是为了能吻你的女朋友.
girlfriend.
本∶对,就是这样的.
Ben: Ok, you got me.
麦琪∶什么?不是为了寻求帮助?
Maggie: What?So this wasn't a cry for help?
本∶稍稍.
Ben: In a way.
麦琪∶哦!我真是不懂男人.
Maggie: Oh I don't understand males.
杰森∶看卡格雷和啦斯不会让你学到任何东西..
Jason: You're not going to learn anything by watching Cagney and Lacey
本∶我也不懂女人.
Ben: I don't understand women.
杰森∶卡格雷和啦斯也不能帮到你.
Jason: Cagney and Lacey can't help you there either.
麦琪∶杰森,你不是在为你儿子的行为而自豪吧?
Maggie: Jason, you're not saying that you are actually proud of your son's behavior
杰森∶没有,麦琪.我希望本能学会怎么样来尊重女人,作为人类,而不是一个性别歧视者.尤物,开玩笑,开玩笑.
Jason: No I'm not Maggie.I want Ben to learn to respect women, as human
beings, not a sex objects.Cutie.Joke, joke
本∶能不能先让我完成我的电影?
Ben: Can I at least finish my movie?
麦琪∶还有另一个场景?
Maggie: There's another scene?
本∶是的.是大场景.
Ben: Yeah.It's the big scene.
大结局,我打算请你和爸爸也参加进来.
The big finish, and I was going to ask you and dad to be in it.
杰森∶耶,本.我演美国总统.
Jason: Yeah Ben.And I'm the president of the United States.
(本的电影)
(Ben's film)
杰森(演布什总统)∶你的荣誉勋章,吉姆.
Jason (Playing President Bush): Here's your medal of honor Jim.
为你职责之外的勇敢.
For bravery above and beyond the call of duty.
本∶非常感谢,总统先生.
Ben: Thank you very much Mr.President.
麦琪(演芭芭拉布什)∶我可以说几句吗?年轻人?
Maggie (Playing Barbara Bush): May I say something young man?
本∶布什夫人,事实上你根本没有任何台词.
Ben: You see Mrs.Bush, you don't actually have any lines here.
麦琪∶但是你要明白,不管什么时候,
Maggie: But you see any time an upstanding American boy tries to kiss
一个出色的美国男孩想以各种手段骗女孩子的吻的行为都是错误的,明白了吗?
a girl under false pretenses, its wrong.Got it?
本∶明白了,妈妈.
Ben: Yes mum.
麦琪∶你会发现年轻的美国女人都是那么的聪明,她们是不会被这些愚蠢的手段所骗的.
Maggie: And you'll find that young American women are much too clever to fall for such silly ploys.
(现实生活)
(Real life)
劳拉林∶本,你在拍摄一个没有我参加的场景?
Laura-Lynn: Ben, you are shooting a scene without me?
本∶你在这里干什么 ?
Ben: What are you doing here?
劳拉林∶抱歉,总统夫妇.
Laura-Lynn: Excuse me Mr.and Mrs.President.
我一直在想今天发生的事情,我觉得我自己错的太离谱了.
I've been thinking about what happened today and I was so wrong.
你的电影就像是给我的另一种形式的情书.我就是那个机智,
Your movie was kind of a video love letter to me.
时髦,久经世故的,
The savvy stylish sophisticated woman whose giddiness makes you dizzy.
光环让你眼花缭乱的女人.你根本就不是想要摸我.
You didn't want to grope me at all.
本∶我们终于明白彼此了.
Ben: Finally we understand each other.
劳拉林∶我已经准备好重新开工了.
Laura-Lynn: I'm ready to go back to work now.
本∶那我们为什么还要浪费时间在这个没劲的场景呢?
Ben: So what are we wasting our time on this dead beat scene for?
让我们回去拍海滩的场景吧.
Let's go back to the beach.
麦琪∶本,你的电影怎么样?
Maggie: Ben, what about your movie?
本∶结束了.
Ben: Its over.
杰森∶芭芭拉,看起来这个房子是完全属于我们俩了.
Jason: Well Barbara, it looks like you and me have the whole house all to ourselves.
麦琪∶哦,乔治.
本∶你们能不能再接一吻?我刚才没拍下来.
00:22:14,500
Maggie: Oh George. Ben: Could you kiss again?I missed it.